



+46 (0) 76 319 33 76



dejan.dojcinoski@yahoo.com



linkedin.com/in/dejandojcinoski

LANGUAGES

Swedish, Native English, Full Professional Proficiency Norwegian, Professional Working Proficiency

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Bootstrap 5
Cordova v 10.0.0
Git / GitHub
HTML5 / CSS3/ JavaScript v ES6
Java SE7
MySQL
PHP
phpMyAdmin
Postman
Python 3.7
SQL

Visual Studio Code / Visual Studio

PERSONAL SKILLS

Adaptability
Communication
Creative
Problem Solving
Teamwork
Time Management
Want to Develop
Work Ethic

CERTIFICATIONS

DevNet Associate

CCNA: Introduction to Networks

CCNA: Switching, Routing, and Wireless Essentials CCNA: Enterprise Networking, Security & Automation

DEJAN DOJCINOSKI

Software Developer

PROFILE

I am a recently graduated software developer with BSc (Honours) Computing & IT. As a mature age graduate, I bring a many years of front-line customer experience to my work.

During my studies I was able to learn from many industry-experienced IT professional in areas such as Web development, Java coding, APP development, Agile delivery, Software Engineering, and the different aspects and applications of the software development lifecycle.

My degree explored many modern aspects of the industry, such as networking, though my particular areas of interest are with software development and delivery of both commercial products and customer business applications.

IT EXPERIENCE

As part of my final assessment in my education, I completed a project where I created a mobile application to bring the neighborhood closer together by acquire and offer assistance where e.g. databases, requirements gathering, and the Scrum methodology were used. This project used all aspects of the system development life cycle as well as project management.

EDUCATION

The Open University, Milton Keynes, UK
Bachelor of Science (Honours) Computing & IT

- IT Project Delivery
- Software Engineering
- Cisco networking (CCNA) parts 1 & 2
- Web, Mobile & Cloud Technologies
- Object Oriented Java Programming
- Algorithms, Data Structures & Computability
- Web Design and Delivery

WORK EXPERIENCE

August 2018 – December 2021 FFAB Trading AB, Sales manager

- Responsible for new sales and additional sales to existing customers
- Development of new products Document handling

November 2014 – July 2018 Laxå Tryckeri AB, Sales manager

- Responsible for planing, incomming orders, new sales and additional sales to existing customers
- Creation or changes of existing printed matter using InDesign

INTERESTS

Family activities • Homefix • Sports • Travels • Video-games

VOLUNTEERING WORK

August 2021 - Ongoing

Head coach for Laxå IF, Boys Under 10 / 11